Rejolin Sobia SM

Junior Developer

2 years of experience in developing full stack enterprise web applications. I am a self-motivated and self-taught professional who likes to solve problems. Efficient and enthusiastic team player with good communication skills. Seeking a position in an environment which emphasizes teamwork and encourages learning. Involved in front-end, back-end side of the application development.

Employment History

may 2022 -Present

Seeking a position

Egrove Systems Pvt Ltd Type your text

Working on Elite Site Optimizer Project

Upgrading Python and Django to the latest version in Elite Site Optimizer Project

Analysed the project flow and working on to provide api to the frontend team

2021 - 2022

Junior Developer

Trinity Software Technologies

Good experience as a full stack python developer

Created projects using Django Framework

Responsible in treating database and it's validations and authorization with MYSOL

Worked on HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript and jQuery

2020 - 2021

Python Django - Intern

Trinity Technologies

Worked with various Python Integrated Development Environments like Idle, Jupyter Notebook, NetBeans, Ananconda and Visual Studio Code Created database using MYSQL, wrote several queries to extract datas from database

Django framework was used in developing web applications to implement model view model view template architecture

Designed a static website for an educational platform

Completed a nursery project and Pet sitter project

Created a registration form using python along with database access

2018 - 2019

Online Tutor

Focus Edumatics Pvt Ltd

Provide private instruction to individual or small group of students to improve academic performance, improve occupational skills or prepare academic or occupational tests

Provide feedback to students using positive reinforcements techniques to encourage, motivate or build confidence in students

Education History

2013 - 2017

BE - ECE

Nehru Institute of Engineering and Technology

Info

Address

10-10/5, Authivilai, Neyyoor street, Kanyakumari district, 629802 Tamilnadu,India,

Phone

9629780374

Email

srejolin@gmail.com

Skills

Python

Django

HTML5

CSS3

Bootstrap

MYSQL

Flask

Javascript

jQuery

Postgresql

Languages

English

Proficient

Tamil

Proficient